Guide to the Roger Sherman (1721-1793) Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Part II
  - FINANCIAL AND LEGAL DOCUMENTS, 1734-1792; 3
    - Legal documents, 1754-1786
      - DS, Sherman to Badlam, Libra 67 Folio 212. (Box 2, Folder 26A)
        Deed by Roger Sherman conveying a tract of land in Stoughton to Stephan Badlam. Original entered February 7, 1743 in the Record of Deeds for the County of Suffolk, Massachusetts, Libra 67 Folio 212. Attested as "a true copy" by F. Semple, Registrar, [no date].
  - GENEALOGICAL, 1855-1904; 4
    - Copies (typed) of legal documents relating to the Sherman family in England, 1473-1628: 12 wills; 5 commissions to administer goods of those deceased; a list of 11 baptisms, 1 marriage, and 2 burials. [23] p. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - [Copies of documents relating to the Sherman family in the United States] (Box 2, Folder 28)
      AD, concerning the watch placed at Caleb Church's mill, (signed) Hugh Mason and John Sherman. 1776 Oct 4, [n.p.]. 1 p. (Nineteenth century copy?); Photocopy of a petition to Congress to prohibit the delivery of mail on Sunday. 1828 Dec 11, Boston. [2] p.
    - Hoar, Senator George Frisbie (1826-1904), grandson of Roger Sherman.
      - Correspondence relating to Sherman family history, 1885-1903 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence relating to the divorce of John and Rebecca (Austin) Sherman in 1793; collected by George F. Hoar in 1898 and 1902. (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Miscellaneous papers relating to the Sherman family (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence (typed copies) with George Sewall Boutwell, on the Republican Party and national politics., 1899 December 27-1900 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Ames, Ellis (1809-1884) (Box 2, Folder 33)
      3 articles (typescript) on Roger Sherman copied from the Massapoag Journal, 1855. Mar 3,4 p.; Aug 4, 8 p.; Aug 11, ll p. (See also letter of Sarah W. Ames to Senator George F. Hoar, April 28, 1899 in folder 29.)
    - Sherman, Roger (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Bib, worn by Roger Sherman and presented to G. F. Hoar by his mother, ca. 1856